Hello hello ji very good morning now and
reporting live from Goa so last few
videos I made in the mountains in St.
Martin social media what do you
live in the mountains in that or the last two videos
I made here not like this in Delhi but because of them I have come back from anywhere else or
item or Randhawa dry
flour some videos should be made for you so today
's meeting is in Indore which I have
described you also know that if we take
30 policies of Swaad then everything is not
covered means if we take
health insurance then our team
will be everything will be taken care of Mitthu
cheers a prominent that with this cute policy
you have to keep notification for that
and this I will tell you the side is the speed is
98% and the policy can change a bit
now you can do this people residing in it
what are the politicians so it depends
I have used this for you so
phone 6000 years - - drink water Kunwar
feel iPhone  Shravani Karma brings videos of
your personal life
trying to commit suicide and
trying to make a fool of yourself by establishing that our
company is silent Dhingra verification going on
towards office videos Monday tuition
is superhit investigation means that
if someone wants to get
their treatment done then click subscribe
and secondly if there is
no other then I will
attach it in great detail in the description box. There is a
problem in the policies but there are some
conditions for that firstly the
doctor will advise that this surgery is immediately necessary but the
surgery should be done on them
related to it
if it
is above the above otherwise
it is not done then do
not even think about
changing
these
policies basically there is no choice in
your next hazards and adventure
sports if you are participating in adventure sports
and you get injured then it becomes
necessary to doctor job
button hospitalization is a Bansal system
operating a breach of low pressure program from that side you get injured
and need hospitalization  Even if it is not a
criminal end, there will be no dream defect.
Next, activity providers are
tied to this hospital. This relationship
health insurance policy, you can check the
policy document information
that that hospital to break the ice, they do not
get Annie Besant. So if you want to get limited
treatment correction and it will be that Amazon itself,
but PM bus Mandi, then
keep this in mind if you want to plus,
so next is treatment and
alcoholism withdrawal on any substance, that
means if you are going for
any constipation, relax
this treatment, you can see the day.
Next, flight rolls are different where you
go for your glass due to medically necessary
condition, then that is also the building. Next,
respectful when we get our eye side correction
surgery done by submitting a complaint to Amazon Maxis
contract, which is
simple and infertility as a medical scientist, do not forget to subscribe to the channel,
click the subscribe button,
if you are
not subscribed, but there is an
increase in
which you can do this, then that is
lock open termination of pregnancy.  Even then
Kabaddi is the next charge related to the
hospital which is not in the recipe, the
hospital is the one where the charges increase, for example, if you
want your comfort then there is a surcharge, it is dividing by 40, so please do that, the
subscription is not covered
and this is the reason, for this
reason Bigg Boss
replacement therapy is
not covered and is
not covered in the policy, next in the policy is
if you get an interaction with the media then there is
no money for that, which
turned out to be not significant, it is
not medically necessary, but if you have to take treatment due to
relationship and IT work pressure, then that
treatment is also if you
try to go to an international school, then that
neurodevelopmental
mental retardation can be
referred to someone, so it is
important to know, so it is
important to make it, for this
you can ask a
question in the last month, if you have
not yet subscribed to our channel, do
subscribe now, we will keep adding new videos
for you, there are tabs for this,
so come and there
is full detail in the policy,
now to log in you can see that no one  A
I'm in college
[music]